<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: India | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/india/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-10T16:34:03-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Travel]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-31T12:17:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I figured that coming to the end of the year and about the 3/4 mark of the trip it'd be worth doing a synopsis of everything that's happened so far.  At this point I've been on the road for a little more than four and a half months, having left NYC August 13th.</p>

<p>I've been to 33 "places", (meaning spots I've spent at least one night in) and 12 countries.  I think Brazil is the place I spent the most time at around 1 month and will add another 2 weeks in February.</p>

<p>Excluding the countries I actually visited, I've met fellow travelers from:</p>

<p>Sweeden
Denmark
Holland
England
Australia
Ireland
France
Spain
Bolivia
Scotland
Germany
Italy
Croatia
South Africa
Russia
Austria
Israel
Mexico
Bulgaria</p>

<p>Definitely the most common countries are Aussies by far, then English, Israel, then oddly Sweeden.</p>

<p>Next year I'll be in Argentina (Mendoza, Bariloche &amp; El Calafate (Patagonia)), back to NYC for one week at the end of January.  Then two weeks in Northern Brazil and Salvador, then making my way down to Rio for carnival, then to Peru for two weeks (Lima and Cusco for Machu Pichu) then finally home to NYC with a possible stop in SF for skiing and/or Austin Texas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than 5 Less Than 10]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/17/more-than-5-less-than-10/"/>
    <updated>2009-08-17T19:25:40-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/17/more-than-5-less-than-10</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I'm trying to hit at least 5 and most likely less than 10 countries in two continents over the next 4-6 months.  The trip was supposed to start in India but due to delays with work I had to skip it.  I still had to fly into Delhi, down to Mumbai, and take a cab from the domestic to international terminals in Mumbai.  For some reason the terminals are not connected and it takes about 30 minutes to travel 10km to the international terminal.  Just that 30 minute ride through Mumbai was a pretty eye opening experience.  I was struck first by the massive amount of people everywhere.  The level of poverty was also at a level I had never experienced.  People walk across the highways in bare feet.  A family surrounded my car and was knocking on the windows begging for food.</p>

<p>My short time in India really drove home the point that we are incredibly lucky to have been born where we are.  When KG screamed "anything is possible" he should've qualified it with "as long as you grew up in a country with social mobility".  The whole concept of a caste system is antithetical to how Americans perceive the world.  While I often see people unhappy in their work in NY, they at least get to choose their miserable lives.  It is not what we choose, but the choice itself that we should be thankful for.<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/08/img_0009.jpg" alt="Taxi Ride in Mumbai" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
