<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Bali | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/bali/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-09T10:08:58-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Travel]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-31T12:17:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I figured that coming to the end of the year and about the 3/4 mark of the trip it'd be worth doing a synopsis of everything that's happened so far.  At this point I've been on the road for a little more than four and a half months, having left NYC August 13th.</p>

<p>I've been to 33 "places", (meaning spots I've spent at least one night in) and 12 countries.  I think Brazil is the place I spent the most time at around 1 month and will add another 2 weeks in February.</p>

<p>Excluding the countries I actually visited, I've met fellow travelers from:</p>

<p>Sweeden
Denmark
Holland
England
Australia
Ireland
France
Spain
Bolivia
Scotland
Germany
Italy
Croatia
South Africa
Russia
Austria
Israel
Mexico
Bulgaria</p>

<p>Definitely the most common countries are Aussies by far, then English, Israel, then oddly Sweeden.</p>

<p>Next year I'll be in Argentina (Mendoza, Bariloche &amp; El Calafate (Patagonia)), back to NYC for one week at the end of January.  Then two weeks in Northern Brazil and Salvador, then making my way down to Rio for carnival, then to Peru for two weeks (Lima and Cusco for Machu Pichu) then finally home to NYC with a possible stop in SF for skiing and/or Austin Texas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tallest Man in Asia]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-31T01:28:41-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just wanted to note that it has felt so great being the tallest person everywhere I go.  When I get on a subway, I’m at least a head taller than just about everyone on the train.  It makes me feel like a giant badass.  Just wanted to share that.  If you’re a short guy, come to China/Japan and feel like a baller.</p>

<p>The negative to this is all doorways are built like 6 inches to a foot shorter.  I've banged my head an innumerable amount of times.  You'd think you'd adjust to it, but you'd be wrong.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last Night Out In Bali]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/09/07/last-night-out-in-bali/"/>
    <updated>2009-09-07T08:51:41-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/09/07/last-night-out-in-bali</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The last night out in Bali was a pretty good time.  We started off the night with some great Sushi and then headed to a bar around the corner that was sort of a divey sort of bar.  One of the great ideas Balinesian clubs/bars have come up with is employing hot girls who are combination bartenders/hostess/just paid to hang out with the partrons.  Even though you know it's their job to chat you up, who doesn't like conversations with fun friendly people?  It makes the atmosphere of the bar just that much better.  American bars need to follow the lead on this one.</p>

<p>After the dive bar we headed to return our surf boards and ended up with a jam session at Toba's surf shop.  Bain and one of the surf shop guys, (I'm blanking out on his name but I want to say Ro?) played guitars and me and Adam threw down some verses.  Apparently we were both singers in previous lives.  After that we headed towards vi ai pi which was hosting it's grand opening and had free drinks.  It was kind of a weak scene so early in the night though so we checked out Joe's Place which had Sound Rebel (a local Balinesian Reggae band) playing some great jams.  We sat and watched for about an hour and they played some great tunes.  I drank some Arak, a local rice based liquor, that is banned on Gili due to 26 people having died from drinking it.  My curiosity outweighed my usual distaste for risk and I tried some and really liked it.  After Joe's Place we headed over to Sky Garden.  Sky Garden, per usual, was the hot spot and had a pretty good scene going on.  We watched some fire dancers, cruised around the different levels and then settled down on the dance floor.  I met a white girl who ran a surf camp in Bali, lived in Bali, and had just gotten divorced.  Unfortunately about 30 minutes after I met my ideal woman a bunch of Aussies got in a fight right next to me and I caught a beer bottle to the head which opened up a nice gash on my forehead.  I had to leave to go take care of it and so my night ended a little sooner than I would have liked.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Balinesian Girlfriend]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/09/06/my-balinesian-girlfriend/"/>
    <updated>2009-09-06T05:55:52-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/09/06/my-balinesian-girlfriend</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We kept the villa for two nights, and then Leigh left so we figured it was crazy to split the villa three ways so we went back to Kuta.  Every time I walked by this one massage parlor one of the girls would say hi handsome how are you!  So today when everyone left to go back, I decided to go chat her up.  Her name is Katlina and she's really cool.  I got a massage and we kicked it for a few hours today.  She wanted to get drinks tonight after she gets out of work but my plane is leaving an hour after she gets out of work and I'd miss it.<br/>
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back in Bali]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/09/06/141/"/>
    <updated>2009-09-06T05:43:02-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/09/06/141</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We were pretty sick of Kuta, so we looked into a nicer place in Seminyak.  We went to check out some private villas to see what they cost.  When I found out they were 320 per room for two rooms, I was sold.  Unfortunately, about an hour later, we found out that it was not local currency, but USD.  I went to talk to them about our little miscommunication and to see if they’d take 240 USD for the room which would be 60 a person.  They agreed to give it to us for 250, and we decided to keep it as it was one of the most insanely beautiful places we’d ever seen.  The place came with a maid, laundry, private pool, four bedrooms, open air bathroom, just absolutely stunning.</p>

<p>[caption id="attachment_135" align="aligncenter" width="500" caption="Seminyak Villa Modeling"]<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/09/mg_2772.jpg" alt="Seminyak Villa Modeling" />[/caption]
[caption id="attachment_136" align="aligncenter" width="500" caption="Villa at Night"]<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/09/mg_2784.jpg" alt="Villa at Night" />[/caption]
<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/09/mg_2790.jpg" alt="_MG_2790" />[caption id="attachment_139" align="aligncenter" width="500" caption="Bedroom"]<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/09/mg_2786.jpg" alt="Bedroom" />[/caption]
<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/09/mg_2793.jpg" alt="_MG_2793" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
