<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-09T10:08:35-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Day 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/09/paris-day-4/"/>
    <updated>2010-10-09T22:39:32-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/09/paris-day-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Woke up really late again, and had a slow start and then a quick breakfast.  We decided the one big thing we wanted to get done was the Louvre so we headed over there.  Turns out the Louvre sucks, and the art there is terrible.  The Mona Lisa may be the worst painting I have ever seen.  However, I liked the Spanish painters the best, followed by the French, and the Italians the least.  I did like the really massive paintings as I think it&#8217;s impressive to be able to create something so large without getting lost in the details.  After the Louvre, we came back to the apt for naps and some snacks, Euchre, beers, and then out again.  We bailed on the electro dance party we were planning to attend due to a 30 Euro cover and decided to go to this favela chic place which definitely looked like a favela.  Pre favela we went to some super high end bar very similar to death and co in the east village.  Super expensive really really well made drinks, very LES styled insides and a pretty dapper bouncer.  After a few rounds there we headed to the favela place and we were really pumped but they assured us there was no way they would let in 4 dudes with no chicks.  So we headed to our plan B but were unable to find it.  Along the way we stopped for gyros and met two French girls on vacation in Paris.  They had some destination in mind and invited us to join but we all walked around aimlessly before finally finding it.  By the time we got there though, the place was pretty empty/weird scene, like 90 year old man with no shirt on weird, so we decided to bail and just get a decent night of sleep.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Day 3]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/07/paris-day-3/"/>
    <updated>2010-10-07T22:34:23-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/07/paris-day-3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Spent another long day walking around the city capped off by a visit to the Arc D&#8217;Triomphe.  Pretty amazing view format the top, 8 roads converging in a circle at the Arc.  Really great day of walking around and Russell explaining all this stuff going on.  Naps and then dinner with Leigh Russ me and Fo at some famous steak restaurant which is Peter Lugers style.  You just tell them how many people and they bring you steak and french fries in the most ludicrous steak sauce.  Everyone licked their plates clean.  Our waitress was this really sweet french woman who chatted with us all night and made jokes about the fact that i had hidden a wine bottle under the table for apres diner and forrest opened the coke she brought him with the wine opener we have been carrying around with us.  After dinner we met up with Jon Beardsley and some other girls who knew Emma Haberman from high school.  We went to some jesus bar which had religious paraphernalia all over the bar and looked like a frat basement with a bathroom with porn magazine cut outs all over the place.  It was a chill bar and we all just kicked it for a while and then decided to get some wine and head down to the water.  Somehow Russ had met some boxer who had fallen in love with him and legitimately would not go away, so he said we were all going home, and was planning on going with this guy, trying to ditch him at some point and then coming to find us.  Within like 5 minutes i get a call from Russ saying that this guy asked some guy for 3 Euro and when the guy said no and lightly pushed him away this guy smoked him in the face, the dudes face exploded, sirens started blaring and Russ ran away.  He met up with us on the banks of the Seine where we camped out and went through a few bottles of wine.  There seemed to be a bit of a party on the other side of the river so Russ and I went to check it out but it had slowly dispersed by the time we got there.  There was a high class party on a boat parked on the side of the river and we tried to sneak/talk our way in but there security guards didn&#8217;t think it was comical in the least and quickly escorted us back onto the shore.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Day 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/05/paris-day-2/"/>
    <updated>2010-10-05T22:29:42-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/05/paris-day-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Woke up late and did a long walk towards Notre Dame and the little thing on the hill.  Notre Dame is pretty impressive as to be expected, and just in general the cities architecture is magnificent, never seen anything like it.  Around mid day my sickness really started to drain me so we sat down for a minute and then decided to take the metro to our destination.  We hopped out and climbed up a big hill and at the top got a pretty spectacular view of the city.  After that we headed home and took some naps before meeting up with Herbert and Meg for the Spain world cup game.  I was still so exhausted that I had to bail and go back to sleep and skipped dinner and then met up with them around midnight at some bars post dinner.  The 3 hour nap was necessary and I felt a million times better and we proceeded to crush some beers and shots and champagne at a Rugby bar as we ran into some of Russ&#8217; old friends who were Rugby players.  Then Herbert lost her necklace so Russ went to go look for it with her and we headed to some other bar that supposedly had a dance floor but it was literally all old dudes like 50&#8217;s and so we went back to the front and got 4 beers and 4 shots for 80 EURO!  After that we headed home.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Day 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/03/paris-day-1/"/>
    <updated>2010-10-03T22:23:51-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/03/paris-day-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Woke up late and did a long walk towards Notre Dame and the little thing on the hill.  Notre Dame is pretty impressive as to be expected, and just in general the cities architecture is magnificent, never seen anything like it.  Around mid day my sickness really started to drain me so we sat down for a minute and then decided to take the metro to our destination.  We hopped out and climbed up a big hill and at the top got a pretty spectacular view of the city.  After that we headed home and took some naps before meeting up with Herbert and Meg for the Spain world cup game.  I was still so exhausted that I had to bail and go back to sleep and skipped dinner and then met up with them around midnight at some bars post dinner.  The 3 hour nap was necessary and I felt a million times better and we proceeded to crush some beers and shots and champagne at a Rugby bar as we ran into some of Russ&#8217; old friends who were Rugby players.  Then Herbert lost her necklace so Russ went to go look for it with her and we headed to some other bar that supposedly had a dance floor but it was literally all old dudes like 50&#8217;s and so we went back to the front and got 4 beers and 4 shots for 80 EURO!  After that we headed home.[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving Copenhagen]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/01/leaving-copenhagen/"/>
    <updated>2010-10-01T22:16:53-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/10/01/leaving-copenhagen</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The girls came with us to Tivoli which was cool but a major rip off.  We did one ride which was basically swings that spin around a really tall pole which gives you an amazing view of Copenhagen, a truly beautiful city.  Other than that we chilled on the green, walked around and had some churros basically just killing time before we had to head to the airport for our flight to Paris.</p>

<p>Arrived late at night and all crashed at Leighs apt, walked down the street to grab a beer and sample the Paris night life in the square right down from Leigh&#8217;s apartment.  We then decided to walk towards Notre Dame and grab some wine and drink it by the Seine and Louvre.  Pretty chill evening and then Russ took me to his old neighborhood to show me the apt he and Suzie party used to live in.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copenhagen Day 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/30/copenhagen-day-1/"/>
    <updated>2010-09-30T22:04:35-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/30/copenhagen-day-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We roused slowly and made our way into town to get some sushi to see if we could start putting healthy things into our bodies and nurse them back to health.  After sushi, we did some laundry, went to the park for some wiffle ball, and generally just attempted to waste the day away.  Fo and Russ went to an internet cafe for coffee and catching up on &#8220;real life&#8221; while Emma and I went shopping in preparation for the nights bbq.  Pernille and Helene arrived around 7:30 and they cooked up some pesto pasta.  In addition we made peppers, salad, burgers, potato salad, and hot dogs.  A pretty epic feast.  Emmas rooftop is a luxury style with hardwood on the top running the length of the building along with wood tables and comfy chairs, lights and a propane grill.  It&#8217;s pretty baller and I&#8217;m pumped to make good use of it this summer.  Tine showed up late to the feast around 11 with one of her friends Tove and we played a game of pass the pigs, drank a few bottles of wine and headed into her bedroom for some boce, jack daniels, and general mischief.  Emma and I passed out early because we were both sick.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roskilde Day 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/29/day-4/"/>
    <updated>2010-09-29T21:57:29-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/29/day-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I woke up Day 4 having lost my voice and having such severe pain in my throat that it felt like someone had put a hot poker down my throat, not sure how that happened.  The camp was an absolute disaster and everyone felt like death.  We decided to bail on Day 4 of the festival and just head home early.  After getting some breakfast and water in us though, we felt a little bit better and decided just to hang around and participate in the destruction.  All around us, the festival came apart.  At around 5am that morning the &#8220;animal camp&#8221; across the street from us had put on the theme from the lion king and massacred their camp before exiting.  We used the whiffle ball batt to swing at just about anything that might explode in an interesting fashion, mayonnaise, tennis balls, wine bags, beer cans, etc.  We were all in that delirious post 3 day binge still hungover and feeling a little crazy haze that you sometimes get.  It was a pretty awesome morning capped by filling 5 gallon freezing cold water jugs and dumping them on members of our campsite who had fallen asleep or were caught unaware.  No no one had the energy to attempt any of the concerts despite a pretty good lineup for the last day, so we all played wiffle ball, ran around a bit, and then headed out in the early afternoon.  The devastation at the festival was pretty amazing.</p>

<p>We made it back to Emma&#8217;s apartment a severely depleted crew and decided to go out for a quick bite.  I got pizza, and the rest of the crew got pasta from a new place that had opened up.  Everything was delightful and we made it back just as it started to get dark around 10:30PM.  We threw in wedding crashers and everyone passed out.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roskilde Day 3]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/28/roskilde-day-3/"/>
    <updated>2010-09-28T21:54:23-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/28/roskilde-day-3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Day 3 was more of the same.  Probably a noon wakeup, a little food, and then Kings of Convenience and Vampire Weekend.  Kings of Convenience was chill and we just sat in the grass at the back.  Vampire Weekend was really fun and somehow we lucked out and got right up at the front I think because we cut a ton of people who had been waiting in line.  After that we returned to camp for dinner and more wiffle ball.  Again we required a pull of scotch and bought 3 more cases of beer to start getting festive.  The American flag drew a lot of attention and a lot of Americans came by to take a few swings.  Met a bunch of cool people.<br/>
[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM9n3m79tg0]
The highlight was a sportscaster worthy grab that I made where I jumped in the air over this guy but sort of clipped him with my shoulder.  I barely grazed him but he honestly acted like I had punched him in the face.  I apologized profusely and he ended up giving US HIS CASE OF BEER.  Still unclear how that one worked itself out.  We were also able to watch football on a giant screen while we were playing which was cool.  After wiffle ball we headed back to the camp for more beer bowling.  We got a good crew together and all headed out to see Prodigy who was supposed to be epic.  However when we got there, it kind of blew.  So we stayed for about 20 minutes and then set out to cause trouble.  I think Russ and I lost everyone somehow so we went to buy a bottle of Jack and go on some missions.  We ended up meeting two Danish girls in the line for booze and ended up hanging out all night with them.  One of them spoke fluent French so of course Russell fell in love with her and at some point I lost them and went wandering by myself and ran into Forrest at some point.  There was some early morning dance party going on so we tried to get into that but it wasn&#8217;t really happening so we went and hung out at the DJ tent before crashing.<br/>
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roskilde Day 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/28/roskilde-day-2/"/>
    <updated>2010-09-28T21:53:58-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/28/roskilde-day-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We probably roused around 11AM and went to get food.  We all began to properly meet each other and all drew our spirit animals in marker on each other.  I was Sweden Shark, in honor of my favorite guy I met traveling, Forrest was Relaxing Giraffe, Emma&#8217;s was blobfish, Pernille was a Manatee, Tine was a Guinea Pig.  To get the day into gear Fo, Russ and Laessa (Pernille&#8217;s brother) went to play whiffle ball.  They brough the Scotch and beers and an American flag that we were wearing as a cape.   As people came to join the game for at bats, they were required to take a pull of scotch before their ups.  This was when we met this awesome German guy, Christoph.  Emma and I went to join them but couldn&#8217;t find them so instead went to the skate park which had dudes in wheelchairs (not handicapped) throwing each other off ramps.  When we returned to the camp Russ and Fo had made friends with the camp across the street from us (the Animal Camp) which was a bunch of hilarious characters, a bunch of Danes who all had animal costumes (Cockroach, Cats etc) and they were playing beer bowling where you have two chairs at one end and two at the other end facing each other at opposite ends of a &#8220;bowling lane&#8221;.  In between your chairs you have a beer can, and you roll a soccer ball at the other teams beer can.  There is a judge who is in charge of &#8220;punishing&#8221; people, which basically consists of handing out arbitrary beer penalties on a whim.<br/>
[Edited for inappropriate content]
[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sr7mfMNKKuw]
Leigh arrived from France to much fanfare at the camp and probably received a better reception than most of the rockstars on stage at the festival.  We were so pumped and he added some much needed energy to the camp.  He arrived just in time to see the nephew concert.  Nephew is a Danish rock band which started by some famous Danish comedian who decided he wanted to be in a band too.  I have never seen a crowd go so insane for a concert.  It&#8217;s kind of one of those things that&#8217;s a mix between national pride and love for the music.  The concert was by far the best I&#8217;ve ever been too, literally 60,000 screaming Danes going fucking apeshit for these guys.  We had a group of about 10 of us at the concert and we were just jumping around and screaming even though we couldn&#8217;t understand anything they were saying.  At the end of the concert they had some guest DJs who got lifted down and hung just above the stage by the giant crane.  People went crazy.  So funny that the best concert we went to we didn&#8217;t understand a word of.  After the concert we all went on various missions.  The four of us ended up at a Norwegian tent of about 15 people who were really chill.   One of us got naked in exchange for beers.  We sat and kicked it with them till about sunrise and then went to the DJ tent.  It was a camp that was set up like a house with a DJ booth cut into the front of the house.  They were a bunch of young Danes who were pretty chill and loved us New Yorkers.  After a long night we finally hit the sack.<br/>
[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N16x2dbV4ZQ]
[gallery columns=&#8221;4&#8221; orderby=&#8221;title&#8221;]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roskilde! (Late thanks to Russell)]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/23/roskilde-late-thanks-to-russell/"/>
    <updated>2010-09-23T13:17:16-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/09/23/roskilde-late-thanks-to-russell</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We rolled into Copenhagen at 6AM after a 6 hour flight to Iceland, and another 4.5 hour flight into Copenhagen.  Emma surprised us by meeting us in the airport which was pretty awesome.  We headed into Copenhagen to Ostebro where she lives to drop off our stuff.  Russ and Fo went to a cafe to get some breakfast and Emma and I chilled at her apartment.  Then we packed our stuff up and headed to the festival.  We took a train to Central Station and then another train to Roskilde.  The last train we took was super old and had spray paint all over it and looked like a party train.  We were probably the oldest people on the train.  We opened a bottle of Glenfiddich we had picked up at the duty free shop in JFK (crazy cheap) and started passing it around but surprisingly no one on the train wanted any.  What kind of 20 year olds don&#8217;t want to hit the bottle before a 4 day festival?  The mood in the train was strangely somber for being 5 minutes away from the festival and I started to get worried that it might not live up to expectations.  However, once inside the festival gates, we knew we were in the right place.</p>

<p>The festival grounds stretch honestly as far as the eye can see, and that&#8217;s just the West camp, there is a whole &#8216;nother larger camp, the East camp.  About 70,000 people camp out, and every campsite has a pavilion style tent provided by the festival.  The whole setup is remarkably orderly.  Everything is set up in a grid with walkways every 40 feet or so similar to manhattan city blocks.  We found our campsite, and met the girls and fellow Campsite mates we&#8217;d be crashing with.  There were 6 girls, and two guys, in addition to me Fo Russ and Leigh (who was to join us the next night).  We immediately started crushing beers and scotch and when we were sufficiently soused we hooked up the ghetto blaster with some old school rap tunes and started roaming the grounds.  Within about 30 minutes a group of Danish girls dressed up in Lederhosen requested to give me a sponge bath in one of those little kiddy pools.  Then they washed my hair.  Everyone was in tears laughing, and it was at this point any doubt that the festival would live up to it&#8217;s promise vanished.<br/>
[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CLafBYaLCpk]
We met an Irish guy, Cormac, at the same campsite who was there just by himself who had just stumbled across the festival.  He left home at 13 and has been traveling ever since.  He was in jail for 2 years because he had walked into the wrong pub in London with an Irish football jersey on and got the shit beaten out of him.  When they finally let him up he grabbed the first barstool he could find and smashed it through a guys face.  I asked him if he would do it differently if he could go back in time, and he said nope, but if he could change it, he would have just run after he did it.  Fucking hilarious character.  He lives in Sweeden now with his pregnant girlfriend.</p>

<p>When Emma and Tine first explained Roskilde to me, I looked at the lineup and was so excited to see about 10-15 shows.  However they laughed and told me there was no way I&#8217;d want to go to all those shows, that Roskilde is about the people and the camping, the music is just sort of a distraction.  I thought they were idiots, and just didn&#8217;t understand how much I love music.  However, after being at Roskilde for a few hours you realize that you could care less whether you see even one show.  Overall, I made it to LCD Soundsystem, Vampire Weekend, Kings of Convenience, Florence and the Machine, and Nephew and I think that was it.</p>

<p>By the time Tine and I went to LCD Soundsystem, we were both thoroughly wasted.  We got to the show about 30 minutes after it started and it was PACKED.  However, Tine was in the zone, and was just touching people on the shoulder and whispering things in their ear, and the red seas would part, we literally made it to the front row from the back of a 5,000 person crowd.  I just held onto her hand and watched the magic happen.  When we finally got to the front we absolutely rocked out.  LCD killed it per usual.
[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8FyiW8sYGms]
 After the show we took as many pictures with the random people we met on the way back to the campsite.  The rest of the evening was relatively uneventful, although Forrest met two Sweedish girls and went to the Gorillaz concert with them, and I can&#8217;t remember where Russell went.  The other crazy thing about Roskilde is that it&#8217;s light till about midnight and then gets light again at like 4am.  So almost the entire time you are there it is light out.  The first night I think we hit the sack at about 4AM.
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldwide Breezy Tour Summer 2010]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/06/29/worldwide-breezy-tour-summer-2010/"/>
    <updated>2010-06-29T16:13:17-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/06/29/worldwide-breezy-tour-summer-2010</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve been debating whether or not I&#8217;d continue writing this blog, seeing as I got burned out in Brazil and never even wrote about Carnival.  However I was inspired by Nicola with the great title she gave me.  Me Russ and Forrest head out tomorrow for the first leg of what looks to be an epic summer.  We leave JFK at 2pm, fly through Iceland and arrive in Copenhagen at 6AM.  Emma is meeting us at the train station and we are going to drop our stuff off at her place before proceeding to the Roskilde Festival.  The festival looks pretty insane, 70,000 people and a killer lineup of bands.  The girls were nice enough to get all our stuff all set up so all we have to do is just roll in and tents and chairs and stuff will already be waiting for us.  All we have to bring is booze and a sense of adventure!  I&#8217;ve spent quite a lot of time picking up gear for the festival as we are going to be the American camp and as such have to represent properly.  I have face paint, fabric markers to make shirts, an LED belt buckle, red white and blue wayfarers, an american flag, a ghetto blaster with an ipod hookup, and probably a bunch of other crap I&#8217;ve already forgotten.  Leigh flies in to join us at the festival Friday and leaves Sunday.  After the festival we spend two nights in Copenhagen at Emma&#8217;s and then fly out on the night of the 6th to Leigh&#8217;s place in Paris.  According to Russ his place is in a sweet location, west village style. Pretty pumped to see Europe, and try out my French for the first time.  I finally feel like a true blue blooded Ivy league douchebag backpacking around Europe for a summer!  When I&#8217;m talking to a girl who goes, OMG I LOOOOVE PARIS I can say OMG ME TOO LOL!!!  Not sure if my stories this summer will be as good for blogging as I can no longer shamelessly embarrass myself with women, but I hope to put up some good pics and share some good moments from time to time.  Hopefully having a girlfriend won&#8217;t preclude tons of fun adventures this summer.  At the worst I can just tell some stories about sketchy Leigh.  I guess there&#8217;s only one way to find out.  Juice out.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love is a Punch in the Throat]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/04/01/love-is-a-punch-in-the-throat/"/>
    <updated>2010-04-01T00:01:23-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/04/01/love-is-a-punch-in-the-throat</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Copied verbatim from Brett Martin
http://timetogetstarted.wordpress.com/2010/03/31/love-is-a-punch-in-the-throat/
Love is a punch in the throat
&#8221;
Thanks to my girlfriend @brycelongton for digging this up.</p>

<p>reposted from http://queserasera.org/archives/000790.html</p>

<p>Love</p>

<p>I think there are two kinds of love. Well, maybe three if you count Kill Bill Vol. 2, which was just an excuse for Quentin Tarantino to gaze at Uma Thurman through a camera lens and then lay claim to her with a giant cinematic facial at the end by shooting his name across her face in huge letters that might as well have been dripping down the screen. Anyway, I think there are two kinds of love. One is the kind of love where a person already has decided the things they want to happen to them, the things they desperately want and need and associate with love, they’ve mapped them out on their own heart beforehand, and they’re just trying to find someone to do them with. They’ve already decided that love = zany photobooth pictures and sharing their favorite movie on the couch once a week and saying this one pet name and them both liking the same band and going to the same coffeeshop and looking up and smiling over a book. So every person they date, they take them on the same walk to the same place and take the same pictures and pose the same pose and try the same lean-in and give the same mix tape, just giving the routine they want a test drive over and over again until it sticks, and then they get all the comforts that come with the routine of loving someone who holds the same things dear, or is at least game for holding your things dear with you.</p>

<p>And then there’s the other kind of love, that kind that sneaks up on you and punches you in the throat, and every part of it seems crazy and foreign at first, from the person and how they make you feel to the new things you find yourself doing, and you’re almost weirded out by how strange it is, and how you’re simultaneously repelled and attracted to it, and you might roll your eyes at it all and say, whatever, I’m not in love, I’m just doing this for awhile, but then one day you realize you want that strange new routine and person and it’s more love than anything else has ever been ever in your whole entire life, ever.</p>

<p>Interchangeable photobooth people, I wish you well, but I’ll take my punch in the throat.&#8221;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isla Grande]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/isla-grande/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T22:52:16-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/isla-grande</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Isla Grande was just an incredible week.  The island is super chill, no vehicles, and really only developed on about a mile strip of beachfront on one part of the island.  You can take day boat trips to other beaches, or do long beautiful hikes along the coastline.  I had gotten to know Lex and Ben pretty well so we headed out on a 2 hour hike to Lopes Mendes beach which was supposed to be one of the top beaches in the world and it did not disappoint.  The hike was brutally hot, and exhausting but enjoyable nonetheless.  Once we got to Lopes Mendes we realized it was well worth the trip.  It is by far the most gorgeous beach I&#8217;ve ever been to, trumping anything I saw anywhere in Hawaii.  Just perfect deserted, long, deep white sand beach with the most perfectly clear aqua blue water to top it off.  We had a great day of just chilling on the beach, listening to my ipod, and reading.  After a great day we caught the boat back to our hostel and kicked it on the deck with beers and some food.</p>

<p>The rest of the week was pretty much a repeat of our first few days.  Boat trips to Lopes Mendes, super lazy days, and nights partying at the hostel.  I met a great new crew the last few nights that I was there.  Dan, Lucy, Gemma and Claire, all Brits and two Dutch girls whose names I&#8217;ve forgotten.  We all headed out to get dinner, and on the way, an insane rainstorm hit us, and the whole island lost power.  Crazy wind and rain started pounding us on the beach and we ran into town to find a pizza place.  We had a great dinner, Dan was one of the funniest guys I&#8217;d ever met, and Lucy told us a great spooning story: She was feeling lonely one week, so she called up one of her guy friends to arrange a &#8220;spooning&#8221; date.  Now first of all I&#8217;ve never had a date with a girl friend with the express intent of spooning and nothing more.  I mean who signs up for sexual frustration?  Anyways, the guys all hesitant about it all week, and is like trying to make up all these excuses.  I&#8217;m not sure&#8230;etc etc.  And finally he&#8217;s like Lucy I just don&#8217;t feel comfortable with this.  So she&#8217;s like what is the big deal with spooning?  And he&#8217;s like dude I just don&#8217;t feel comfortable sticking a spoon up your ass!  Record stops&#8230;.WHAT?!?!?! So if you missed that, somehow the whole time she was talking about spooning he thought she wanted him to stick a spoon up her ass.  Oh you Brits kill me.</p>

<p>After dinner we headed out to Aquarius, the hostel next to ours for a dance party which ended up being pretty awesome.  Unfortunately the rest of the stories from Ilha Grande are not fit for public presentation.[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paraty]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/paraty/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T21:51:27-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/paraty</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After a crazy week of work in NYC and a great time seeing all my old friends, I hopped a plane back to BA, then to Sao Paulo, and then caught an overnight bus to Paraty.  This was probably the biggest disaster of the whole trip.  Sometime during the night, we stopped off at some random bus stop, and I asked the bus driver if I could go get food.  I went to get food and returned about 4 minutes later to find that the bus had left without me.  In a panic i tried talking to various official looking people but basically got nowhere other than to confirm there was another bus coming later that night, and that they would get me on it.  I begged them to call the bus driver on his radio and try and secure my belongings but my weak portuguese could not get that across, ironically my dictionary was on the bus with the rest of my stuff&#8230;Another bus arrived around 2 in the morning and I hopped on and arrived in Paraty around 5AM.  I took a cab to the hostel and waited for morning to come so I could try and get my stuff.  To make a long story short, I went back to the bus terminal, found out they didn&#8217;t have my stuff, and had a hostel employee call the main company to explain the situation.  At that point I only had the clothes on my back and pretty much ruled out getting my stuff back.  Luckily, a bunch of kids in the hostel I had met at the Millhouse hostel in BA and so I joined up with them to go to Trinidade beach. There were about 7 different beaches in the area and we went kinda beach hopping all afternoon. It was brutally hot but the beaches were awesome and we made a good day of it.  We finished by doing a little hike up a river/waterfall sort of spot and checked out this sort of cave you can slip into.  We met some cool locals and chilled with them for a bit.  We headed back towards the main beach where a few restaurants were and grabbed some food and beers.  Then out of nowhere Olivia showed up and we had one of those OMG what are you doing here moments even though I had been planning on meeting her in Paraty we were an hours bus ride away from the our hostel where we were supposed to meet up.  Pablo, one of the hostel employees had brought her to Trinidade to look for me assuming that&#8217;s the only place I could be if I wasn&#8217;t in town.  We all headed back as it got a bit later and had a nice chill night back at the hostel.  Some of Liv&#8217;s friends from Floripa were staying at her hostel right next to mine, two Aussies named Lex and Ben who were super chill and we all kicked it and drank beers in the main square.  The next day we did this big boat trip to a bunch of little beaches.  The boat was huge and had nice white lounger chairs on it so me and Liv just chilled out, talked story, and jumped off the boat and swam around when we got to the various island swim spots.  An amazing day.</p>

<p>After about two days in Paraty Liv was losing it because she had no AC in her room and was basically dripping with sweat all night so we decided to move on to Isla Grande.  We caught a nice bus to Angra Dos Reis, where the end of the line bus terminal was, and Liv went with me to get my stuff.  We got back all my stuff, except computer, hard drive, cables, headphones etc, but were able to recover my camera after much negotiating and yelling.  We missed the cheap ferry so instead took a sweet catamaran ride to Isla Grande.  It was well worth the extra money as we got to sit on the roof of the boat and drink beers in the sun and chill out for the 45 minute ride.  We met some hilarious Canadians and probably the most beautiful girl I&#8217;ve ever seen who happened to be French and I got to practice my French with.  We rolled into Isla Grande and had only booked one night at Che Lagarto which luckily was one of the sickest hostels I&#8217;ve ever stayed at.  It was about a 5 minute walk down the beach, sort of at one end of the town, and was built with a deck over the water.  So you could sit out and eat breakfast or dinner on the water every morning/night for 35 Reais a night.  The first night we really lucked out with the one room with the balcony on the water and A/C.  We met up with a giant group of Aussies, a few of whom were girls Liv had hung out with in Floripa and got drinks with them on the beach.  After a few drinks we hit up rodizio (all you can eat meat) for dinner and then went back to our hostel for a band/party on the porch.[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Chaltan]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-chaltan/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T21:19:09-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-chaltan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>El Chaltan was a quick 4 hour bus ride from El Calafate and I was able to catch the 4PM bus after seeing the glacier and get up there by nightfall.  I checked into the Aubergue Patagonia hostel which was really nice and quaint.  Chaltan the town itself is bizzare in that it seems to just appear out of nowhere.  It looks like a bunch of ice fishing shacks in the middle of a lake.  After checking into my hostel, I went to use the internet to email Sophie to let her know I had her memory card, and on the way back I heard from all the way down the street the sound of that distinctive accent.  I yelled down the road Sophie! And she came running towards me.  She had been drinking quite a bit with two new friends, a married British couple James and Amy who were awesome.  We went to one of the few watering holes in the town and ordered up a few rounds of Quilmes.  After a healthy amount of drinking given that we were supposed to be up early to do a hike the next day we all hit the hay.  In the morning we made some food for the trip and set out for the glacier hike.  The hike was gorgeous all the way and we caught a rare beautiful day in Chaltan for it.  You walk up through a pass in the mountains towards a lake and valley at the base of some mountains that leads to a glacier.  By the end of the hike the wind is so strong you can literally lean all your weight into the wind and it will hold you up.  The last mile of the trek was really crazy and fun as I&#8217;d never been in wind nearly that strong and we were jumping off rocks and being carried in the wind a few feet further than you&#8217;d normally fly.  We hunkered down in a little bunker made out of rocks and ate lunch and snapped some pictures by the lake.  After lunch we had a nice hike back home.  Sophie wasn&#8217;t staying in our hostel and so the three of us cooked a nice chili and rice meal and then met Sophie for some beers again.  Everyone was heading out the next day so I got my own gear, tent, gloves, hat, sleeping bag and made up an overnight pack for my hike to the Fitzroy peak, the crown jewel of Chaltan.  The hike itself wasn&#8217;t too hard as it&#8217;s only 4 hours each way and I was camping overnight so I only did 4 hours that day, but it was pretty cold and rainy all the way up and unfortunately visibility was almost 0 so I missed on on a lot of the spectacular beauty of the hike.  I got up to the campground a little later than expected because I got lost, and set up my campsite.  I met a cool Polish guy and we chatted for a few hours but unfortunately I hadn&#8217;t brought any books because my kindle got stolen in Bariloche.  I did my best to fall asleep early as I was told that watching the sunrise at Fitzroy was magnificent.</p>

<p>The next day I woke up around 4 AM and realized I hadn&#8217;t brought a flashlight and it was pitch dark.  I made friends with some Israelis who had the same plan and they shared some tea and crackers with me to get the blood flowing.  We all set off around 4:30 AM to catch the sunrise.  It was unbelievably cold and I only had a long sleeved tshirt w/shell and jeans on so I was freezing.  Luckily I decided to bring my sleeping bag for warmth and when we got to the spot they had scouted out to catch the sunrise i zipped myself up cocoon style.  The sunrise was a bit cloudy but we did get some 10 second breaks in the clouds which provided for some great if sparing views.  It was an amazing morning and I had a great time with the big Israeli crew.  Once it got a bit lighter I returned to camp and broke down my tent and packed up my gear and headed home.  Unfortunately I missed the views on the way home as well due to rainy cloudy conditions but I was still happy with the trip.  After a few days in Chaltan I returned to Calafate and caught a plane up to Buenos Aires and then out of BA back to NYC![gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Calafate]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-calafate/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T18:06:16-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-calafate</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The journey to El Calafate was surprisingly good considering it was about 28 hours.  They played American movies the whole time except while we were sleeping, and i was seated next to a cool Kiwi, Sophie.  We chatted for a good portion of the trip and watched movies the rest of the time.  28 hours on a bus sounded horrible, but the terrain was gorgeous and passed by in a flash.  We arrived in Calafate and I invited Sophie to join me at America Del Sul Hostel.  The hostel picked us up at the bus station which was a nice little perk, and we settled into one of the most gorgeous hostels I&#8217;ve stayed in.  It had a giant living room with giant bay windows overlooking the mountains and lakes and had nice sofas and a big area for group dinners.  I decided to splurge and buy into that nights asado.  Right after checking in, Olivia and Mary, the Scottish and British girl who I had met at Independencia and disliked, waltzed into my room and we had one of those OMG what are you doing here moments!  I ended up getting to know them better and really liking them.  Mary was feeling under the weather so she took a long nap, but Olivia, Sophie and I all played cards and drank Quilmes and wine until late.  Sophie had to leave in the morning for El Chaltan and couldn&#8217;t find her memory card for her camera anywhere.  I knew I had seen it on my bed but couldn&#8217;t remember what I did with it.  Right after she left for her bus I found it in my wallet and was really happy as she had left in tears and I knew I&#8217;d be heading to meet her later that evening.  Olivia, Mary and I took a tour to the Perito Moreno glacier.  Definitely one of the highlights of my life.  I had no idea it would be so amazing.  The glacier is much larger than you can imagine going in and just gorgeous in the sunlight.  There are a ton of walkways that allow you to get really close to it and watch giant chunks of it break off and fall furiously smashing into the water.  Every time a chunk fell into the water it sounded like an explosion.  I had an awesome time with Olivia and Mary and they ended up being two of my favorites on the whole trip.  [gallery]</p>

<p>[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NkIW8XSmJWY]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barylochay]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/barylochay/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T17:27:52-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/barylochay</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I left Mendoza on the way to the lakes region of Patagonia, namely Bariloche.  It was another overnight 16 hour bus journey and I was a little concerned about my housing situation in Bariloche as the few hostels I had contacted had said they didn&#8217;t have room for the first night of my arrival.  I got into the center of town around 5PM and immediately set about trying to find a room.  Almost all the hostels are located on the same strip which took a bit of time to find but once I was there it was pretty easy to ascertain whether or not they had space.  One hostel was nice enough to let me put my stuff down there while I looked for rooms and I slowly worked my way through every hostel in the town.  Around 9PM I realized there wasn&#8217;t one bed in the whole town, hostel or hotel and started to get a little nervous.  It was really cold and was drizzling.  I had planned on just throwing on a few layers of clothes and sleeping outside but there really wasn&#8217;t anywhere to sleep outside and it was unbearably cold.  I went back to the hostel that had let me put my stuff there and asked if they&#8217;d be willing to let me crash on a couch for the night and luckily there was a cute girl behind the desk who I could flirt with and she acquiesced.  I went to another hostel she recommended that had a bar and people to hang out with for a beer.  I ran into Chris, a guy I had met at Independencia and he was with another friend of his, John, he&#8217;d met in BA.  Chris was in the same situation as me and I told him to go talk to the people at my hostel and they hooked him up too.  We had a few beers and hit the sack early.</p>

<p>The next day we did an amazing bike tour called the 7 lakes bike tour because as you  might guess you cycle around 7 lakes.  It&#8217;s gorgeous terrain although slightly hillier than I was in shape for and we finished the day absolutely exhausted.  During the bike ride we stopped in a little town with sort of a craft fair and got sausage and beers to give us some energy for the trip, and did a few little side trail hikes.  Per usual, I fell in love with the girl who ran the bike rental place and we chilled a bit with her when we finished the day up.  I was pretty keen on relaxing while I was in Patagonia so I didn&#8217;t &#8220;go out&#8221; at all while I was there.  On my last day in Bariloche we did the &#8220;Otto&#8221; hike which is a pretty steep hike up a beautiful mountain that overlooks the whole valley.  It&#8217;s supposed to be one of the top 10 views in the world and when we reached the top we were not dissappointed.  It was about an hour up to the top and from the top you had a 360 degree view of all the mountains.  Just incredible.  Kind of looked like pictures of Scotland I&#8217;d seen.  I stayed at Pudu hostel which was really cool.  Everyone who worked there was really chill and I met a bunch of really friendly, rustic sort of travelers.  I left Bariloche after 3 nights and 2 and a half days of pure Patagonian beauty ready for the wonders of the end of the world.  [gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mendoza's Clubs]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/mendozas-clubs/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T17:15:04-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/mendozas-clubs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The highlight of my trip to Mendoza&#8217;s nightlife had to be our crazy trip outside of the city.  A few nights prior Josh had been out to some clubs outside of the city, which sounded sketchy when it had first been suggested but he came back reporting that these were the biggest clubs he had ever been to and that they had a crazy fun time.  Josh&#8217;s 2 Irish and 1 British buddies came by the hostel and we all pregamed together before migrating to an Irish bar in town.  After everyone was fired up to go out, we all got in taxis and headed to the club, except plans went awry when none of josh&#8217;s friends came in our cab, and he forgot where this place was.  So we just described to the taxi driver what we were looking for.  A club outside of the city that held about 30,000 people.  The driver was like ahh  si and we headed out.  We drove for about 30 minutes into a really remote area that reminded me of some wealthy part of Sao Paulo.  Like giant fields and huge Haciendas with giant walls.  We rolled up to the gate of one of them to be told by the guards toting weapons that we were not in the right place.  Not to be deterred the taxi driver told us he&#8217;d find something.  About 20 minutes further out of town we rolled up to the largest club I&#8217;ve ever seen by at least 5 times.  It made the clubs in Cancun look like children&#8217;s forts. Oddly we had to pay for our drinks before we got into the club, so Josh and I bought 4 drinks each not knowing what the deal was.  Mel and another girl who had to be home at like 6AM to catch a flight were with us and we all went to pick up our drinks.  When I asked for a red bull vodka, they gave me a full glass of vodka, and a full redbull.  My kind of club.  We all lost each other within minutes and I proceeded to dance and party solo for the rest of the night.  I randomly ran into Josh at about 6AM when the club closed at a food stand as I was staaaaarving.  We grabbed a cab and headed home both smiling and in awe of the evening.[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Andes Tour]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/high-andes-tour/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T16:59:37-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/high-andes-tour</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There was an amazing amount of outdoorsy stuff to do in Mendoza, and most of it pretty cheap, but I only had $1000 USD until I could get back to the states and get another debit card, so I was trying to be extremely conservative.  The cheapest/best thing I heard about was called the high Andes tour.  A bus came and picked us up at 7AM and took us on a tour up to the top of the Andes/Chile border for 100 pesos.  Mel came with me and it was an awesome day.  We stopped at a lot of lame little touristsy spots along the way and they let us get out and take pics, but nothing really compared to going 3000 meters up the mountain in a van and getting up to the top of the mountains and the Chilean border.  It was unbelievably cold, which makes sense because we were so high, but I had no warm clothes with me.  We go to run around a bit and snap pics and then we headed down to the base camp for an amazing meal.  Mel and I had bought a bottle of wine earlier and cracked that as well as a huge tray of meat and stews and various Argentinian dishes.  It was a delightful way to end the day and we headed home with bellies full and smiles on our faces.</p>

<p>After we got home Charles and I decided to make dinner for everyone so we headed to the supermarket and got ingredients for some kind of pasta dish he wanted to cook, got some Quilmes beer and some crazy cheap Malbec and cooked up a fine meal for our friends in the hostel.  We had another great night of cards and beers and hit the sack early.  [gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mendoza]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/mendoza/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T16:52:44-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/mendoza</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I took off from BA after an absolutely insane two weeks.  What an amazing city.  The bus ride to Mendoza was relatively reasonable at around 8 hours and passed without incident.  It was suggested to me that I stay at Independencia Hostel by some friends in Millhouse so I inquired for directions in my broken spanish and set out walking towards town as it was only a 15 minute walk.  Independencia was just what I was looking for.  A chill, clean, spacious hostel with about 35 beds.  It had a huge outdoor courtyard where everyone seemed to chill, eat, drink, smoke and mingle.  After about 5 minutes sitting in the main living room inside watching TV I ran into Charles who was this crazy British guy who lived in LA and who I&#8217;d partied with quite a bit in BA.  Normally I would&#8217;ve been stoked to see him but I was a bit apprehensive because my body had literally shut down after all the partying in BA.  The first night we decided to stay in and play cards in the courtyard.  We invited Mel, an British woman who had been living in Sydney and a Dutch girl whose name I never could pronounce to play cards and drink beers with us.  We ended up playing asshole, or as the rest of the world calls it, shithead all night and ended up having a blast.  Two Aussie chicks rolled in around 10 PM absolutely shitfaced and could barely walk.  They joined us for cards and were absolutely hilarious and a great addition.<br/>
[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WqSX3TjUt9A]</p>

<p>The next day we woke up hungover but early so we could do Mr. Hugo&#8217;s wine tour which just about everyone in South America will tell you to do.  We rounded up a pretty good crew of around 8 people including another Aussie named Josh who had just arrived minutes before, although two British chicks, Olivia &amp; Mary, and their friend Chris, declined our invitation leading me to believe they sucked.  Mr. Hugo&#8217;s may have been the highlight of all of South America.  You take about an hour bus out to an area with about 10 different vineyards as well as a wine museum, he rents you bikes, and you&#8217;re free for the day to just cruise around and do your thing.  We ended up joining forces with two more Americans we met along the way from Colorado and LA and settled down at a beautiful winery.  They gave us the run through of all the different types of wine and we figured it was cheaper to just buy one of each bottle rather than doing their tasting as we had a huge group of around 15 people.  We had run into another group of Americans (probably the most American&#8217;s I saw anywhere in the world) once we arrived at the winery and they wanted to split the wine with us.  So we all chilled outside in the beautiful courtyard right next to all the vines and slowly worked our way through about 10 bottles of wine.  By the time we were ready to leave everyone was pretty wasted and half the group wanted to head further down the road to check out the last winery.  Mel, the dutch girl, and I all hung back and decided to just meet the rest of the group at Mr. Hugo&#8217;s later as we didn&#8217;t want to bike further away just to turn around and come back as it was getting late in the day.  We arrived back at Mr. Hugo&#8217;s around 6PM and it was an absolute festival.  To set the scene, he runs this company out of his house, so you&#8217;re just sitting at someones house on the side of the road, and he has tons of tables and chairs and benches set out on his front lawn, and speakers just pumping out Argentinian club jams.  All you can drink wine is included with your $25 bike rental so everyone back at the house was waaaasted.  There was probably a big group of about 30 of us and we just kicked it at Mr. Hugo&#8217;s until around 9 when people finally slowed down and hopped the bus back into town.  At this point a bunch of groups split up.  Josh left with a bunch of Canadian girls, and i went back the Americans and Mel to a nice hotel room to shower and get ready for the evening.  There&#8217;s a really cool street in the center of Mendoza which is surprisingly hip and has a ton of cool cafe type bars where everyone sits out on the sidewalks and hangs out.  We chilled and drank some beers and enjoyed a beautiful evening but were all exhausted from the long day of drinking and called it in early.  [youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zlXznkpXAgE]
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
