<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Hong Kong | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/hong-kong/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-10T16:34:03-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Travel]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-31T12:17:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I figured that coming to the end of the year and about the 3/4 mark of the trip it'd be worth doing a synopsis of everything that's happened so far.  At this point I've been on the road for a little more than four and a half months, having left NYC August 13th.</p>

<p>I've been to 33 "places", (meaning spots I've spent at least one night in) and 12 countries.  I think Brazil is the place I spent the most time at around 1 month and will add another 2 weeks in February.</p>

<p>Excluding the countries I actually visited, I've met fellow travelers from:</p>

<p>Sweeden
Denmark
Holland
England
Australia
Ireland
France
Spain
Bolivia
Scotland
Germany
Italy
Croatia
South Africa
Russia
Austria
Israel
Mexico
Bulgaria</p>

<p>Definitely the most common countries are Aussies by far, then English, Israel, then oddly Sweeden.</p>

<p>Next year I'll be in Argentina (Mendoza, Bariloche &amp; El Calafate (Patagonia)), back to NYC for one week at the end of January.  Then two weeks in Northern Brazil and Salvador, then making my way down to Rio for carnival, then to Peru for two weeks (Lima and Cusco for Machu Pichu) then finally home to NYC with a possible stop in SF for skiing and/or Austin Texas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tallest Man in Asia]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-31T01:28:41-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just wanted to note that it has felt so great being the tallest person everywhere I go.  When I get on a subway, I’m at least a head taller than just about everyone on the train.  It makes me feel like a giant badass.  Just wanted to share that.  If you’re a short guy, come to China/Japan and feel like a baller.</p>

<p>The negative to this is all doorways are built like 6 inches to a foot shorter.  I've banged my head an innumerable amount of times.  You'd think you'd adjust to it, but you'd be wrong.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last Night in Hong Kong]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/24/last-night-in-hong-kong/"/>
    <updated>2009-08-24T23:18:06-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/24/last-night-in-hong-kong</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Finally got back to Hong Kong after an exhausting flight and train ride.  I can’t remember the last time I was so happy to get somewhere, but returning to Hong Kong feels like returning home after being in China.  We got a room at the Hotel Jen which was awesome, half the price of our other hotel (like 50 USD) centrally located, and so much nicer.  I recommend anyone who visits HK to stay there.  It has an open air rooftop pool, awesome 28th floor bar overlooking the city, and a great buffet breakfast.  We were supposed to meet up with Angad but we waited till about 11:30 PM and he still was at work ( I don’t understand why these finance people do it).  We went to Wung Fan, a great dumpling place on wellington street recommended by Matt.  Headed back to our hotel and drank a bottle of Rum which was terrible.  We took a cab to tonic because it was the only bar we knew of, and then walked around the different bars in central basically following any cute girls we saw.  Hong Kong doesn’t seem like the type of place where you pick a bar and go to it for the night, everyone seems to move in and out of each bar every 10 minutes which is probably due to everything having an open front rather than a door.  The night was pretty fun, went to drop and gecko and a couple other random spots I don’t remember.  We met a bunch of groups of cute girls but nothing really came out of it.  I met the only two black guys I saw in my entire time in HK and they were real chill.  They had just come back from Bali from a wedding of one of the guys tenants.  He must be an awesome landlord to get invited to a tenants wedding.  He said indo girls do not drink or go out, only indo girls out are pro’s.  Grabbed some late night philly cheese steaks and tried to convince some girls we met there to come back to our hotel and jump in the pool (which we knew was closed) with us to no avail.  Then headed back to the hotel.  Packed up our stuff and headed out to the airport as we had a 9am flight.  3rd time pulling an all nighter on the trip so far.  The Hong Kong nightlife is awesome, and probably would be more awesome if you lived there, or spent more time getting into the scene.</p>

<p>[caption id="attachment_52" align="aligncenter" width="500" caption="No idea who this girl is"]<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/08/img_0082.jpg" alt="No idea who this girl is" />[/caption]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maclehose Trail]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/21/maclehose-trail/"/>
    <updated>2009-08-21T04:39:01-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/21/maclehose-trail</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Matt took us on an epic hike on Monday called the Maclehose trail.  We did the second of a 10 part trail.  It was 12K and one of the most beautiful hikes I’ve ever been on.  The terrain was really hilly and you are basically walking through the mountains down to beaches and then back up through the mountains.  We stopped at Big Wave Beach which was oddly named given that there wasn’t even a hint of any waves.  They were renting surfboards at the beach which was quite the tease because Leigh and I had been hoping the whole hike that we’d discover some waves and be able to mess around with some long boards but alas it was not to be.  It must have been about 90 degrees and we all were completely soaked with sweat about an hour into the hike.  The water at big wave bay was really warm and felt incredible after a few hours of hiking.  After a brief stop to play in the water we continued on and hiked the rest of the trail.  The end of the trail overlooks some gorgeous blue rivers and then takes you back to a main road.  After this hike I was pretty amazed that Matt had run this entire trail (all 100KM) in a competition as we were totally spent after just one section of it. Pics of Hong Kong at flickr</p>

<p><img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/08/mg_1929.jpg" alt="Big Wave Bay" /></p>

<p><img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/08/mg_1943.jpg" alt="Maclehose Trail" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[HK 1st Night Update - Belly Dancing]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/21/hk-1st-night-update-belly-dancing/"/>
    <updated>2009-08-21T04:33:19-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/08/21/hk-1st-night-update-belly-dancing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Somehow I forgot to mention that we went to a restaurant called Habibi our first night in Hong Kong.  Matt said they had good food and there was a sign outside that said they had a free belly dancing show that started in 10 minutes.  The restaurant was middle eastern food (Egyptian?) and the show was really cool.  I got some sort of blue Martini which was terrible.  Oh well, you win some you lose some<img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2009/08/mg_1861.jpg" alt="Belly Dancer" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
