<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Tokyo | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/tokyo/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-10T16:34:03-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Travel]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-31T12:17:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I figured that coming to the end of the year and about the 3/4 mark of the trip it'd be worth doing a synopsis of everything that's happened so far.  At this point I've been on the road for a little more than four and a half months, having left NYC August 13th.</p>

<p>I've been to 33 "places", (meaning spots I've spent at least one night in) and 12 countries.  I think Brazil is the place I spent the most time at around 1 month and will add another 2 weeks in February.</p>

<p>Excluding the countries I actually visited, I've met fellow travelers from:</p>

<p>Sweeden
Denmark
Holland
England
Australia
Ireland
France
Spain
Bolivia
Scotland
Germany
Italy
Croatia
South Africa
Russia
Austria
Israel
Mexico
Bulgaria</p>

<p>Definitely the most common countries are Aussies by far, then English, Israel, then oddly Sweeden.</p>

<p>Next year I'll be in Argentina (Mendoza, Bariloche &amp; El Calafate (Patagonia)), back to NYC for one week at the end of January.  Then two weeks in Northern Brazil and Salvador, then making my way down to Rio for carnival, then to Peru for two weeks (Lima and Cusco for Machu Pichu) then finally home to NYC with a possible stop in SF for skiing and/or Austin Texas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts on Japan]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/13/thoughts-on-japan/"/>
    <updated>2009-11-13T13:42:10-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/13/thoughts-on-japan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First off, I didn’t spend nearly enough time in Japan.  What a cool place.  I wish I had at least a month.  Also if you go, get the rail pass, it’s less than the price of a one way ticket to any major part of Japan but can only be purchased outside of Japan.  So it’s worth buying if you plan on taking even one bullet train ride as it allows you to ride unlimited for 7 days and if you use it even once you’ve already saved money.  I really wanted to go visit a friend of a friend in Kyoto but it was $260 USD for a round trip ticket which seemed crazy for just one day.<br/>
One weird thing about Japan is that tons of people walk around with those Doctors masks on.  I know that SARS must have been a big scare for people over there but really it was years ago, what kind of way is it to go through life wearing a mask constantly.  It’s just ridiculous.  Why not lock yourself up in a giant bubble so no germs can come near you. Also I liked how the Japanese subway stops are numbered.  So you can look at the map once and know ok I’m at stop 3, and going to 9 so you always know how many stops away you are and whether your going in the right direction or if you’ve missed your stop.
I really want to get back to Japan and spend more time outside of Tokyo, and more time enjoying the nightlife.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shinjuku]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/12/shinjuku/"/>
    <updated>2009-11-12T13:06:11-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/12/shinjuku</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After Nikko and the long train ride I decided to go out to see the red light district of Shinjuku, but by the time I was ready to go it had started raining again pretty steadily and I didn’t want to be wandering around the city late at night all wet or miss the last train back and get stuck out all night in the wet and cold.  So I ended up just drinking beers and whiskey alone in my room and chatting on gchat.  The next morning was my last day in Tokyo so I wanted to see Shinjuku which was kind of like the midtown/times square of Tokyo.  I caught an early train that way knowing that I had to catch a 8PM flight.  Shinjuku was cool, very New York Midtown feel but a little bit nicer.  I spent the day just walking around, checking out stores and checking out the architecture.  I found an electonics store that was massive and had a different type of gadget on each floor.  If you know me you know this is pretty much my version of heaven.  They had the most amazing little computers and I was so jealous at the wireless cards speed you could get for these tiny little netbook like devices.  I checked my watch and realized I was running a bit late so ran back to the subway and headed back to the hostel to check out.  On the train I realized the plane was at 7:30 not 8 and I had already left Shinjuku an hour later than I had planned so I panicked and thought I was in danger of missing the plane.  I ran back to the hostel, grabbed my stuff, checked out, and ran back to the subway to head to the airport train.  Luckily I pulled into the airport with about 1:15 till takeoff.  However at the information booth I found out I was at the wrong terminal, so I sprinted to a cab and rode about 5 minutes to the other terminal.  Luckily when I got to the counter they told me to relax and take a deep breath as I had made the plane.  Finally some good plane luck.</p>

<p>[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nikko]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/11/nikko/"/>
    <updated>2009-11-11T13:05:55-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/11/nikko</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I finally got out of Tokyo and decided to do a day trip to Nikko.  The train ride was long, but the seats were comfortable and I was stoked to finally be exploring Japan a little bit.  After a 1.5-2HR ride I arrived at the town center.  I grabbed some food and bought a bus pass that takes you to all the historical sights.  Once you head up into the mountains on the bus you immediately see what all the fuss is about.  Nikko looks like you expect Japan to look like.  Particularly in the fall the trees are turning the most beautiful red’s and oranges and the whole forest looks like it’s on fire.  Interspersed between the trees in the forest are these really cool Monasteries and Temples.  You feel like you’ve stumbled onto an ancient Samurai camp.  Unfortunately all the tours and information are in Japanese so I learned very little about what any of the temples and/or statues actually represented or were used for back in the day.  Despite that, just spending the day wandering through the forests and checking out the temples was sick.  Around 4PM I decided to head further up the mountain so I could check out the onsen (Japanese Baths).  This was another awesome experience.  The lady at the bus stop recommended a hotel on this lake in the mountains.  As I arrived the sun was setting over the mountains and water and the air was crisp and cool.  They give you slippers and a towel and you go into a sort of rustic all wooden building where there’s a changing room and then a 10 by 20 3 foot deep pool.  The whole place reeks of sulfur as I imagine that’s what is causing the natural heating of the water.  You acclimate to the sulfur pretty quickly although I think I breathed through my mouth the whole time.  You shower and wash yourself before you go into the bath and then get into the pool.  I have to say it was kinda weird to be kicking it naked in a shallow pool with like 10 old Japanese dudes, but it was also really cool.  It felt like stepping into a time warp to another world.  The water is so hot and relaxing and you can sort of feel all the minerals seeping into your body and making you healthier (probably totally placebo effect).  The back wall of the onsen was all glass and I sat in the natural hot springs and watched the sun set over the lake.  It was about as relaxing and cool of an experience as I’ve had on the trip.</p>

<p>[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roppongi Hills]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/06/roppongi-hills/"/>
    <updated>2009-11-06T12:56:13-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/11/06/roppongi-hills</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After such a long night out I basically burned a whole day resting.  The day after that unfortunately was pouring rain so I wasn't sure what I was going to get to do.  After talking to some people at breakfast, they suggested I do the Roppongi Hills museum tour.  I checked out the Suntory Art Museum which was actually quite beautiful given that I hate art.  They had an exhibit on Japanese paper.  This included everything from just straight up different types of paper made in the traditional Japanese way, to incredible Oragami type foldings and creations of flowers and really large displays all made of paper.  It was actually really impressive.  After that I headed to the Fuji photo center where they had pretty awesome landscape pictures of all of the most beautiful cities in the world.  I finished up my tour with a visit to the Mori Art Museum which was awesome.  The museum had an exhibition by Ai WeiWei who is a famous Chinese modern artist who got popular during a ten year stint in NYC during the late 80's and early 90's.  His exhibit was actually pretty cool.  He seemed to have this fusion between Western and Eastern art and minimalist combined with contemporary.  The highlight of the visit was actually a movie by another Japanese film artist whose name I neglected to write down.  This sick movie must have come straight out of either Bryan Thomas or Julian Kelly's mind.  The filmmaker put an ad out in a dutch newspaper looking for someone who could tell a really sad personal story on film.  He gets the guy in this tiny little room that's decorated kind of like a spaceship.  The guy starts telling his story which basically consists of meeting the girl of his dreams, getting her pregnant, marrying her, his wife leaving him because of his drinking, and him losing access to his daughter which was emotionally crushing.  The whole time this guy is telling the story he is on the verge of tears.  The filmmaker is dressed like some kind of martian with silver paint all over his face and this bizzare costume.  Every time the guy would get about into the story the filmmaker would interrupt and ask the guy to change his pose, or put something else on to the point of utter ridiculousness.  Check out the pics at the end of the post to see the progression.  Honestly it's something you have to see to believe, i was in tears laughing at this movie.  The poor guy is like pouring his heart out and the filmmaker has him shirtless with like a french bread roll in his mouth by the end.  The climax of the film is the filmmaker sticking his head through a hole in the wall and squealing like a pig while the guy is trying to talk.  It's honestly enough to make you fall of your seat laughing because it's just so f*cked up. [gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
