<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Thailand | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/thailand/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-09T10:08:58-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Travel]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-31T12:17:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I figured that coming to the end of the year and about the 3/4 mark of the trip it'd be worth doing a synopsis of everything that's happened so far.  At this point I've been on the road for a little more than four and a half months, having left NYC August 13th.</p>

<p>I've been to 33 "places", (meaning spots I've spent at least one night in) and 12 countries.  I think Brazil is the place I spent the most time at around 1 month and will add another 2 weeks in February.</p>

<p>Excluding the countries I actually visited, I've met fellow travelers from:</p>

<p>Sweeden
Denmark
Holland
England
Australia
Ireland
France
Spain
Bolivia
Scotland
Germany
Italy
Croatia
South Africa
Russia
Austria
Israel
Mexico
Bulgaria</p>

<p>Definitely the most common countries are Aussies by far, then English, Israel, then oddly Sweeden.</p>

<p>Next year I'll be in Argentina (Mendoza, Bariloche &amp; El Calafate (Patagonia)), back to NYC for one week at the end of January.  Then two weeks in Northern Brazil and Salvador, then making my way down to Rio for carnival, then to Peru for two weeks (Lima and Cusco for Machu Pichu) then finally home to NYC with a possible stop in SF for skiing and/or Austin Texas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tallest Man in Asia]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-31T01:28:41-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just wanted to note that it has felt so great being the tallest person everywhere I go.  When I get on a subway, I’m at least a head taller than just about everyone on the train.  It makes me feel like a giant badass.  Just wanted to share that.  If you’re a short guy, come to China/Japan and feel like a baller.</p>

<p>The negative to this is all doorways are built like 6 inches to a foot shorter.  I've banged my head an innumerable amount of times.  You'd think you'd adjust to it, but you'd be wrong.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeden's Story (Password Protected - Email me for Password)]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/26/sweedens-story-password-protected-email-me-for-password/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-26T01:20:23-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/26/sweedens-story-password-protected-email-me-for-password</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the guys I was travelling with, Sweeden, told me the funniest story I have heard in a long time.  He had been travelling with an Australian for about three months, through China and the Phillipines and finally Thailand before he met up with us on the border of Laos.  So he tells us this story about Ko Pan’Ang where they went out for a typical crazy night out there.  They return at like 3PM the following day, drunk out of their minds, on the back of scooters, with chicks driving them.  This is the last thing Sweeden remembers before complete blackout.  He meets up with his buddy much later that night, and his buddy is not speaking, and looks really morose.  He asks him what’s wrong and his buddy answers, “I fucked a man last night.” To which of course Sweeden wants to know if there’s some story, which of course there is.  He says he went home with this “chick” and “she” started giving him this fantastic blowjob.  After a while “she” tells him “she” wants him to fuck “her” doggystyle in the ass.  Which of course is unorthodox, but not unheard of.  So he’s banging her in the ass for a while and he reaches around front to give her vagina a little massage, at which point he finds two tiny balls, no penis though.  At this point it’s clear to him that he is boning a man, but he is about 80% of the way done, he figures he might as well finish the job.  So he does, and then he goes home and hangs his head in shame.  Thank you Sweeden.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chiang Kong to Luang Prabang]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/16/chiang-kong-to-luang-prabang/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-16T23:17:17-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/16/chiang-kong-to-luang-prabang</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The two English girls are, Louise and Nicola, two Danish girls, Emma and Tine, my friend Pim from Holland, two Aussies, Dave and Keith (who looks and sounds exactly like Jermaine from Flight of the Conchords).  We picked up one Sweede (sp?) in Chiang Kong.<br/>
The bus ride to Chiang Kong is amazing, truly beautiful landscape, exactly how you imagine it will be.  Rice fields and just greenery as far as the eye can see.  Chiang Kong itself is pretty budget.  There is very little to do, and the guest houses aren’t the nicest, but for the one night stopover it’s not the end of the world.  We ended up going to a small bar and playing pool and having some beers.  In the morning we got on the “slow boat” which is a long skinny boat with a top and benches on either side of the boat going all the way back similar to pews in a church.  They sell ice cold beers in the back for 15,000 Kip which is about 2 bucks or you can bring all the alcohol you want on board if you so choose.  You travel down the Mekong river into Laos for two days and one night and it is just breathtakingly beautiful.  There were about a hundred other people on the boat in addition to the group I had been travelling with, including two Americans and a group of about 30 people in their 20s.  About 10 of them had been travelling similarly to my group together since Chiang Mai.  A few from London, Germany, Canada, and others in Europe I don’t remember.  After a few couple of hours, beers were broken out, and the boat got significantly more lively.  We moved the benches around in big circles and got some cards out and starting playing asshole and this horse racing game the other Americans knew.  This was probably the peak of my experience travelling so far.  Being on this boat with so many cool people from so many countries and getting to know them all while floating down a river with spectacular scenery was just perfect.  We played games all day and kicked it and rolled into Pak Bang just in time to catch an incredible sunset.  Our crew all got rooms at a cheap guest house and headed to grab some food.  When we walked into the restaurant that the hotel owner led us too it was completely dark.  Then they flipped the generator on and music and lights and everything came on.  Pretty amusing.  We ordered a bunch of food and they even had an ipod hookup for their sound system so I threw some jams on.  The meal came with free whiskey so we indulged and kicked it for a few hours.  A French girl joined us at the tail end of our meal before heading back to the hotel to play cards and chill.  What a perfect evening.
The second day on the boat started off rough as we had been told the boat left at 10AM so we rolled up at 10 to 10 and everyone was on the boat giving us dirty looks.  Apparently the boat left at 9 so people had been waiting an hour for us to get on.  I’m kind of amazed that they didn’t just leave us there as there was no formal guest list or count of people with tickets.  We went to the back of the boat and didn’t have any seats and were cramped into a small room near the motor.  It was so loud but unsurprisingly the crew of young kids were all back there as well as they had gotten on late also.  We all ended up having another great day though as we were cramped and all could commiserate over the same fate.  The day was capped off by finding out who had stolen my whiskey.  The day before I had bought a liter of whiskey and it had disappeared right as we were getting of the boat when I went to the bathroom for a minute.  One of the girls from Denmark, Emma, said she saw who did it and pointed him out the next day.  So about midday I went up to him and asked him if he had taken a bottle of whiskey off the boat yesterday because my whiskey had disappeared.  He denied having taken it and he seemed like he was being truthful so I dropped it.  About an hour later he came to the back of the boat and told me he had taken it but it had been near a bunch of garbage and we were all leaving so he thought someone had forgotten it.  He had bought me a beer as a gesture of good faith and I was more than happy that he had been a stand up guy about it so I bought him a beer as well and all was well with the world.<br/>
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schnapps]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/15/schnapps/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-15T23:14:43-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/15/schnapps</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a random sidenote but I found it interesting.  The Austrian girls carry around Schnapps with them wherever they go.  This is not the same thing as Schnapps in America that is sweet and really low percentage alcohol.  It is usually between 40-60 percent alcohol but can go up to 80%.  Every family makes it themselves and therefore can distill it to whatever percentage they prefer.  It’s made with fruit and alcohol and is distilled multiple times to get the desired percentage of alcohol.  The girls said there’s was over 60% and I believe them as it burns your throat when it goes down.  They drink it once a day and say it’s very healthy for you.  I think this is a pretty cool tradition.</p>

<p>Right now I’m in a minibus headed to Chiang Khong where you catch the slow boat down the Mekong river to Luang Prabang in Laos.  Rikki and Kieran have to stay in Chang Mai for 5 days to make sure her finger doesn’t get infected, the Austrian girl are going to do a few days in Chang Rai and maybe Pai and then head to Laos.  Me and Pim are in the minibus with two girls from Denmark who I had to embarrassingly ask what language they spoke there (hint: it’s Danish).  They asked me if it was true that all Americans thought that IKEA was the capitol of Sweeden and I said yes because I thought it was hilarious.  We also have an Aussie and two English girls although the Aussie is doing a land tour rather than the 2 day boat trip down the river.  It’s a good crew and I’m excited for the boat trip which is supposed to be gorgeous, and Luang Prabang which is supposed to be insanely beautiful.  Preitty couldn’t get a flight to Chiang Mai so is meeting me in Luang Prabang on Monday.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
