<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Brazil | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/brazil/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-10T16:34:03-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isla Grande]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/isla-grande/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T22:52:16-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/isla-grande</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Isla Grande was just an incredible week.  The island is super chill, no vehicles, and really only developed on about a mile strip of beachfront on one part of the island.  You can take day boat trips to other beaches, or do long beautiful hikes along the coastline.  I had gotten to know Lex and Ben pretty well so we headed out on a 2 hour hike to Lopes Mendes beach which was supposed to be one of the top beaches in the world and it did not disappoint.  The hike was brutally hot, and exhausting but enjoyable nonetheless.  Once we got to Lopes Mendes we realized it was well worth the trip.  It is by far the most gorgeous beach I've ever been to, trumping anything I saw anywhere in Hawaii.  Just perfect deserted, long, deep white sand beach with the most perfectly clear aqua blue water to top it off.  We had a great day of just chilling on the beach, listening to my ipod, and reading.  After a great day we caught the boat back to our hostel and kicked it on the deck with beers and some food.</p>

<p>The rest of the week was pretty much a repeat of our first few days.  Boat trips to Lopes Mendes, super lazy days, and nights partying at the hostel.  I met a great new crew the last few nights that I was there.  Dan, Lucy, Gemma and Claire, all Brits and two Dutch girls whose names I've forgotten.  We all headed out to get dinner, and on the way, an insane rainstorm hit us, and the whole island lost power.  Crazy wind and rain started pounding us on the beach and we ran into town to find a pizza place.  We had a great dinner, Dan was one of the funniest guys I'd ever met, and Lucy told us a great spooning story: She was feeling lonely one week, so she called up one of her guy friends to arrange a "spooning" date.  Now first of all I've never had a date with a girl friend with the express intent of spooning and nothing more.  I mean who signs up for sexual frustration?  Anyways, the guys all hesitant about it all week, and is like trying to make up all these excuses.  I'm not sure...etc etc.  And finally he's like Lucy I just don't feel comfortable with this.  So she's like what is the big deal with spooning?  And he's like dude I just don't feel comfortable sticking a spoon up your ass!  Record stops....WHAT?!?!?! So if you missed that, somehow the whole time she was talking about spooning he thought she wanted him to stick a spoon up her ass.  Oh you Brits kill me.</p>

<p>After dinner we headed out to Aquarius, the hostel next to ours for a dance party which ended up being pretty awesome.  Unfortunately the rest of the stories from Ilha Grande are not fit for public presentation.[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paraty]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/paraty/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T21:51:27-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/paraty</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After a crazy week of work in NYC and a great time seeing all my old friends, I hopped a plane back to BA, then to Sao Paulo, and then caught an overnight bus to Paraty.  This was probably the biggest disaster of the whole trip.  Sometime during the night, we stopped off at some random bus stop, and I asked the bus driver if I could go get food.  I went to get food and returned about 4 minutes later to find that the bus had left without me.  In a panic i tried talking to various official looking people but basically got nowhere other than to confirm there was another bus coming later that night, and that they would get me on it.  I begged them to call the bus driver on his radio and try and secure my belongings but my weak portuguese could not get that across, ironically my dictionary was on the bus with the rest of my stuff...Another bus arrived around 2 in the morning and I hopped on and arrived in Paraty around 5AM.  I took a cab to the hostel and waited for morning to come so I could try and get my stuff.  To make a long story short, I went back to the bus terminal, found out they didn't have my stuff, and had a hostel employee call the main company to explain the situation.  At that point I only had the clothes on my back and pretty much ruled out getting my stuff back.  Luckily, a bunch of kids in the hostel I had met at the Millhouse hostel in BA and so I joined up with them to go to Trinidade beach. There were about 7 different beaches in the area and we went kinda beach hopping all afternoon. It was brutally hot but the beaches were awesome and we made a good day of it.  We finished by doing a little hike up a river/waterfall sort of spot and checked out this sort of cave you can slip into.  We met some cool locals and chilled with them for a bit.  We headed back towards the main beach where a few restaurants were and grabbed some food and beers.  Then out of nowhere Olivia showed up and we had one of those OMG what are you doing here moments even though I had been planning on meeting her in Paraty we were an hours bus ride away from the our hostel where we were supposed to meet up.  Pablo, one of the hostel employees had brought her to Trinidade to look for me assuming that's the only place I could be if I wasn't in town.  We all headed back as it got a bit later and had a nice chill night back at the hostel.  Some of Liv's friends from Floripa were staying at her hostel right next to mine, two Aussies named Lex and Ben who were super chill and we all kicked it and drank beers in the main square.  The next day we did this big boat trip to a bunch of little beaches.  The boat was huge and had nice white lounger chairs on it so me and Liv just chilled out, talked story, and jumped off the boat and swam around when we got to the various island swim spots.  An amazing day.</p>

<p>After about two days in Paraty Liv was losing it because she had no AC in her room and was basically dripping with sweat all night so we decided to move on to Isla Grande.  We caught a nice bus to Angra Dos Reis, where the end of the line bus terminal was, and Liv went with me to get my stuff.  We got back all my stuff, except computer, hard drive, cables, headphones etc, but were able to recover my camera after much negotiating and yelling.  We missed the cheap ferry so instead took a sweet catamaran ride to Isla Grande.  It was well worth the extra money as we got to sit on the roof of the boat and drink beers in the sun and chill out for the 45 minute ride.  We met some hilarious Canadians and probably the most beautiful girl I've ever seen who happened to be French and I got to practice my French with.  We rolled into Isla Grande and had only booked one night at Che Lagarto which luckily was one of the sickest hostels I've ever stayed at.  It was about a 5 minute walk down the beach, sort of at one end of the town, and was built with a deck over the water.  So you could sit out and eat breakfast or dinner on the water every morning/night for 35 Reais a night.  The first night we really lucked out with the one room with the balcony on the water and A/C.  We met up with a giant group of Aussies, a few of whom were girls Liv had hung out with in Floripa and got drinks with them on the beach.  After a few drinks we hit up rodizio (all you can eat meat) for dinner and then went back to our hostel for a band/party on the porch.[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Chaltan]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-chaltan/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T21:19:09-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-chaltan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>El Chaltan was a quick 4 hour bus ride from El Calafate and I was able to catch the 4PM bus after seeing the glacier and get up there by nightfall.  I checked into the Aubergue Patagonia hostel which was really nice and quaint.  Chaltan the town itself is bizzare in that it seems to just appear out of nowhere.  It looks like a bunch of ice fishing shacks in the middle of a lake.  After checking into my hostel, I went to use the internet to email Sophie to let her know I had her memory card, and on the way back I heard from all the way down the street the sound of that distinctive accent.  I yelled down the road Sophie! And she came running towards me.  She had been drinking quite a bit with two new friends, a married British couple James and Amy who were awesome.  We went to one of the few watering holes in the town and ordered up a few rounds of Quilmes.  After a healthy amount of drinking given that we were supposed to be up early to do a hike the next day we all hit the hay.  In the morning we made some food for the trip and set out for the glacier hike.  The hike was gorgeous all the way and we caught a rare beautiful day in Chaltan for it.  You walk up through a pass in the mountains towards a lake and valley at the base of some mountains that leads to a glacier.  By the end of the hike the wind is so strong you can literally lean all your weight into the wind and it will hold you up.  The last mile of the trek was really crazy and fun as I'd never been in wind nearly that strong and we were jumping off rocks and being carried in the wind a few feet further than you'd normally fly.  We hunkered down in a little bunker made out of rocks and ate lunch and snapped some pictures by the lake.  After lunch we had a nice hike back home.  Sophie wasn't staying in our hostel and so the three of us cooked a nice chili and rice meal and then met Sophie for some beers again.  Everyone was heading out the next day so I got my own gear, tent, gloves, hat, sleeping bag and made up an overnight pack for my hike to the Fitzroy peak, the crown jewel of Chaltan.  The hike itself wasn't too hard as it's only 4 hours each way and I was camping overnight so I only did 4 hours that day, but it was pretty cold and rainy all the way up and unfortunately visibility was almost 0 so I missed on on a lot of the spectacular beauty of the hike.  I got up to the campground a little later than expected because I got lost, and set up my campsite.  I met a cool Polish guy and we chatted for a few hours but unfortunately I hadn't brought any books because my kindle got stolen in Bariloche.  I did my best to fall asleep early as I was told that watching the sunrise at Fitzroy was magnificent.</p>

<p>The next day I woke up around 4 AM and realized I hadn't brought a flashlight and it was pitch dark.  I made friends with some Israelis who had the same plan and they shared some tea and crackers with me to get the blood flowing.  We all set off around 4:30 AM to catch the sunrise.  It was unbelievably cold and I only had a long sleeved tshirt w/shell and jeans on so I was freezing.  Luckily I decided to bring my sleeping bag for warmth and when we got to the spot they had scouted out to catch the sunrise i zipped myself up cocoon style.  The sunrise was a bit cloudy but we did get some 10 second breaks in the clouds which provided for some great if sparing views.  It was an amazing morning and I had a great time with the big Israeli crew.  Once it got a bit lighter I returned to camp and broke down my tent and packed up my gear and headed home.  Unfortunately I missed the views on the way home as well due to rainy cloudy conditions but I was still happy with the trip.  After a few days in Chaltan I returned to Calafate and caught a plane up to Buenos Aires and then out of BA back to NYC![gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Calafate]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-calafate/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T18:06:16-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/el-calafate</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The journey to El Calafate was surprisingly good considering it was about 28 hours.  They played American movies the whole time except while we were sleeping, and i was seated next to a cool Kiwi, Sophie.  We chatted for a good portion of the trip and watched movies the rest of the time.  28 hours on a bus sounded horrible, but the terrain was gorgeous and passed by in a flash.  We arrived in Calafate and I invited Sophie to join me at America Del Sul Hostel.  The hostel picked us up at the bus station which was a nice little perk, and we settled into one of the most gorgeous hostels I've stayed in.  It had a giant living room with giant bay windows overlooking the mountains and lakes and had nice sofas and a big area for group dinners.  I decided to splurge and buy into that nights asado.  Right after checking in, Olivia and Mary, the Scottish and British girl who I had met at Independencia and disliked, waltzed into my room and we had one of those OMG what are you doing here moments!  I ended up getting to know them better and really liking them.  Mary was feeling under the weather so she took a long nap, but Olivia, Sophie and I all played cards and drank Quilmes and wine until late.  Sophie had to leave in the morning for El Chaltan and couldn't find her memory card for her camera anywhere.  I knew I had seen it on my bed but couldn't remember what I did with it.  Right after she left for her bus I found it in my wallet and was really happy as she had left in tears and I knew I'd be heading to meet her later that evening.  Olivia, Mary and I took a tour to the Perito Moreno glacier.  Definitely one of the highlights of my life.  I had no idea it would be so amazing.  The glacier is much larger than you can imagine going in and just gorgeous in the sunlight.  There are a ton of walkways that allow you to get really close to it and watch giant chunks of it break off and fall furiously smashing into the water.  Every time a chunk fell into the water it sounded like an explosion.  I had an awesome time with Olivia and Mary and they ended up being two of my favorites on the whole trip.  [gallery]</p>

<p>[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NkIW8XSmJWY]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barylochay]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/barylochay/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T17:27:52-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/barylochay</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I left Mendoza on the way to the lakes region of Patagonia, namely Bariloche.  It was another overnight 16 hour bus journey and I was a little concerned about my housing situation in Bariloche as the few hostels I had contacted had said they didn't have room for the first night of my arrival.  I got into the center of town around 5PM and immediately set about trying to find a room.  Almost all the hostels are located on the same strip which took a bit of time to find but once I was there it was pretty easy to ascertain whether or not they had space.  One hostel was nice enough to let me put my stuff down there while I looked for rooms and I slowly worked my way through every hostel in the town.  Around 9PM I realized there wasn't one bed in the whole town, hostel or hotel and started to get a little nervous.  It was really cold and was drizzling.  I had planned on just throwing on a few layers of clothes and sleeping outside but there really wasn't anywhere to sleep outside and it was unbearably cold.  I went back to the hostel that had let me put my stuff there and asked if they'd be willing to let me crash on a couch for the night and luckily there was a cute girl behind the desk who I could flirt with and she acquiesced.  I went to another hostel she recommended that had a bar and people to hang out with for a beer.  I ran into Chris, a guy I had met at Independencia and he was with another friend of his, John, he'd met in BA.  Chris was in the same situation as me and I told him to go talk to the people at my hostel and they hooked him up too.  We had a few beers and hit the sack early.</p>

<p>The next day we did an amazing bike tour called the 7 lakes bike tour because as you  might guess you cycle around 7 lakes.  It's gorgeous terrain although slightly hillier than I was in shape for and we finished the day absolutely exhausted.  During the bike ride we stopped in a little town with sort of a craft fair and got sausage and beers to give us some energy for the trip, and did a few little side trail hikes.  Per usual, I fell in love with the girl who ran the bike rental place and we chilled a bit with her when we finished the day up.  I was pretty keen on relaxing while I was in Patagonia so I didn't "go out" at all while I was there.  On my last day in Bariloche we did the "Otto" hike which is a pretty steep hike up a beautiful mountain that overlooks the whole valley.  It's supposed to be one of the top 10 views in the world and when we reached the top we were not dissappointed.  It was about an hour up to the top and from the top you had a 360 degree view of all the mountains.  Just incredible.  Kind of looked like pictures of Scotland I'd seen.  I stayed at Pudu hostel which was really cool.  Everyone who worked there was really chill and I met a bunch of really friendly, rustic sort of travelers.  I left Bariloche after 3 nights and 2 and a half days of pure Patagonian beauty ready for the wonders of the end of the world.  [gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
