<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: China | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/china/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-09T10:08:58-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Travel]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-31T12:17:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I figured that coming to the end of the year and about the 3/4 mark of the trip it'd be worth doing a synopsis of everything that's happened so far.  At this point I've been on the road for a little more than four and a half months, having left NYC August 13th.</p>

<p>I've been to 33 "places", (meaning spots I've spent at least one night in) and 12 countries.  I think Brazil is the place I spent the most time at around 1 month and will add another 2 weeks in February.</p>

<p>Excluding the countries I actually visited, I've met fellow travelers from:</p>

<p>Sweeden
Denmark
Holland
England
Australia
Ireland
France
Spain
Bolivia
Scotland
Germany
Italy
Croatia
South Africa
Russia
Austria
Israel
Mexico
Bulgaria</p>

<p>Definitely the most common countries are Aussies by far, then English, Israel, then oddly Sweeden.</p>

<p>Next year I'll be in Argentina (Mendoza, Bariloche &amp; El Calafate (Patagonia)), back to NYC for one week at the end of January.  Then two weeks in Northern Brazil and Salvador, then making my way down to Rio for carnival, then to Peru for two weeks (Lima and Cusco for Machu Pichu) then finally home to NYC with a possible stop in SF for skiing and/or Austin Texas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The News in China]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/the-news-in-china/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-31T01:32:27-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/the-news-in-china</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Iris told me that the news in China is pretty hilarious.  Its 30 minutes, and it airs every evening.  The first 10 minutes detail all the great things the government did that day.  The second 10 minutes detail how happy all the people in China are.  And the third 10 minutes show how much suffering and unhappiness there is in the Western world.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gays in China]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/gays-in-china/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-31T01:29:28-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/gays-in-china</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just wanted to note that I am really curious what it is like to be a gay person in China or the rest of Asia.  As far as I saw, there aren’t really any gays in China.  This is clearly false, but I’m wondering if they are very repressed and not as flamboyant as in America, or all relegated to certain areas?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tallest Man in Asia]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-31T01:28:41-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/tallest-man-in-asia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just wanted to note that it has felt so great being the tallest person everywhere I go.  When I get on a subway, I’m at least a head taller than just about everyone on the train.  It makes me feel like a giant badass.  Just wanted to share that.  If you’re a short guy, come to China/Japan and feel like a baller.</p>

<p>The negative to this is all doorways are built like 6 inches to a foot shorter.  I've banged my head an innumerable amount of times.  You'd think you'd adjust to it, but you'd be wrong.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Zoo Animal]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/a-zoo-animal/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-31T01:26:59-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/31/a-zoo-animal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It seems that in China, they don’t have the same cultural prohibitions on staring.  Everywhere I go I am met with stares and gawking.  I imagine I get this more than most westerners because I have dark skin and it’s probably pretty rare that they see a wealthy dark westerner travelling through their country.  However, it never ceases to amuse me how much people stare over here.  Also, usually in the states if you catch someone staring they will look away when they get caught.  However, over here, they just keep staring.  Pretty funny.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
