<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Argentina | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/argentina/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-09T10:08:58-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Andes Tour]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/high-andes-tour/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T16:59:37-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/high-andes-tour</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There was an amazing amount of outdoorsy stuff to do in Mendoza, and most of it pretty cheap, but I only had $1000 USD until I could get back to the states and get another debit card, so I was trying to be extremely conservative.  The cheapest/best thing I heard about was called the high Andes tour.  A bus came and picked us up at 7AM and took us on a tour up to the top of the Andes/Chile border for 100 pesos.  Mel came with me and it was an awesome day.  We stopped at a lot of lame little touristsy spots along the way and they let us get out and take pics, but nothing really compared to going 3000 meters up the mountain in a van and getting up to the top of the mountains and the Chilean border.  It was unbelievably cold, which makes sense because we were so high, but I had no warm clothes with me.  We go to run around a bit and snap pics and then we headed down to the base camp for an amazing meal.  Mel and I had bought a bottle of wine earlier and cracked that as well as a huge tray of meat and stews and various Argentinian dishes.  It was a delightful way to end the day and we headed home with bellies full and smiles on our faces.</p>

<p>After we got home Charles and I decided to make dinner for everyone so we headed to the supermarket and got ingredients for some kind of pasta dish he wanted to cook, got some Quilmes beer and some crazy cheap Malbec and cooked up a fine meal for our friends in the hostel.  We had another great night of cards and beers and hit the sack early.  [gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mendoza]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/mendoza/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-31T16:52:44-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/03/31/mendoza</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I took off from BA after an absolutely insane two weeks.  What an amazing city.  The bus ride to Mendoza was relatively reasonable at around 8 hours and passed without incident.  It was suggested to me that I stay at Independencia Hostel by some friends in Millhouse so I inquired for directions in my broken spanish and set out walking towards town as it was only a 15 minute walk.  Independencia was just what I was looking for.  A chill, clean, spacious hostel with about 35 beds.  It had a huge outdoor courtyard where everyone seemed to chill, eat, drink, smoke and mingle.  After about 5 minutes sitting in the main living room inside watching TV I ran into Charles who was this crazy British guy who lived in LA and who I'd partied with quite a bit in BA.  Normally I would've been stoked to see him but I was a bit apprehensive because my body had literally shut down after all the partying in BA.  The first night we decided to stay in and play cards in the courtyard.  We invited Mel, an British woman who had been living in Sydney and a Dutch girl whose name I never could pronounce to play cards and drink beers with us.  We ended up playing asshole, or as the rest of the world calls it, shithead all night and ended up having a blast.  Two Aussie chicks rolled in around 10 PM absolutely shitfaced and could barely walk.  They joined us for cards and were absolutely hilarious and a great addition.<br/>
[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WqSX3TjUt9A]</p>

<p>The next day we woke up hungover but early so we could do Mr. Hugo's wine tour which just about everyone in South America will tell you to do.  We rounded up a pretty good crew of around 8 people including another Aussie named Josh who had just arrived minutes before, although two British chicks, Olivia &amp; Mary, and their friend Chris, declined our invitation leading me to believe they sucked.  Mr. Hugo's may have been the highlight of all of South America.  You take about an hour bus out to an area with about 10 different vineyards as well as a wine museum, he rents you bikes, and you're free for the day to just cruise around and do your thing.  We ended up joining forces with two more Americans we met along the way from Colorado and LA and settled down at a beautiful winery.  They gave us the run through of all the different types of wine and we figured it was cheaper to just buy one of each bottle rather than doing their tasting as we had a huge group of around 15 people.  We had run into another group of Americans (probably the most American's I saw anywhere in the world) once we arrived at the winery and they wanted to split the wine with us.  So we all chilled outside in the beautiful courtyard right next to all the vines and slowly worked our way through about 10 bottles of wine.  By the time we were ready to leave everyone was pretty wasted and half the group wanted to head further down the road to check out the last winery.  Mel, the dutch girl, and I all hung back and decided to just meet the rest of the group at Mr. Hugo's later as we didn't want to bike further away just to turn around and come back as it was getting late in the day.  We arrived back at Mr. Hugo's around 6PM and it was an absolute festival.  To set the scene, he runs this company out of his house, so you're just sitting at someones house on the side of the road, and he has tons of tables and chairs and benches set out on his front lawn, and speakers just pumping out Argentinian club jams.  All you can drink wine is included with your $25 bike rental so everyone back at the house was waaaasted.  There was probably a big group of about 30 of us and we just kicked it at Mr. Hugo's until around 9 when people finally slowed down and hopped the bus back into town.  At this point a bunch of groups split up.  Josh left with a bunch of Canadian girls, and i went back the Americans and Mel to a nice hotel room to shower and get ready for the evening.  There's a really cool street in the center of Mendoza which is surprisingly hip and has a ton of cool cafe type bars where everyone sits out on the sidewalks and hangs out.  We chilled and drank some beers and enjoyed a beautiful evening but were all exhausted from the long day of drinking and called it in early.  [youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zlXznkpXAgE]
[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defeat Stolen From the Jaws of Victory]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/01/24/defeat-stolen-from-the-jaws-of-victory/"/>
    <updated>2010-01-24T10:02:26-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/01/24/defeat-stolen-from-the-jaws-of-victory</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I finally met up with the French girl I met on the bust to BA, Carmen.  We went to Thelonius jazz bar which was really nice.  It was only 20 peso cover and the bar had a really cool ambiance.  We grabbed some seats on the couch and settled in for a great night of Jazz.  We had a couple glasses of wine and my french started to get much better.  I had a great time hanging out with her and speaking French for the first time in ages.  Things were going really well and we went outside to have a cigarette.  I don't know about girls reading this, but I feel like as a guy you hit a point in a date where you're like things are going well, im going to kiss this girl, and you just know things are going to work out.  However, right about when I hit this point, this guy comes out, who she had introduced me to earlier, who starts being all touchy feely with her.  At this point I figure this must be her boyfriend and that things are NOT going to work out for me.  We went back inside and the bar emptied out and it was just sort of the friends of staff after hours crew and we opened a bottle of champagne and sat at the bar and hung out.  At this point I could ask her point blank if that was her boyfriend because he didn't know french and wouldn't know what I was saying.  She told me he was and that he was just being jealous, you know how Argentinian men are.  I told her I thought it was reasonable to be a bit jealous given that she brought another dude to his bar and was being really flirtatious with him.  Oh well, all in all it was a really fun night, despite finding out some bad information a little late in the game.<a href="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2010/01/img_1082.jpg"><img src="http://halfblackhalfamazing.files.wordpress.com/2010/01/img_1082.jpg" alt="" /></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sugar Bar]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/01/22/sugar-bar/"/>
    <updated>2010-01-22T09:48:55-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/01/22/sugar-bar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After La Boca I went to Sugar bar with a couple of the guys I'd been hanging out with.  Sugar bar has 5 peso anything you want happy hour until midnight.  That's about $1.25 USD.  So we chilled there for a couple of hours.  Then we headed over to Bahrein which was having a drum and bass night.  One of the guys we were with was super into drum and bass and the hostel was going to be at the bar so I figured I'd check it out not knowing what drum and bass is.  For the record, drum and bass is really terrible music, in my opinion.  So after about an hour there, I was like I can't take any more of this.  We went outside and tried to find a few other options, but at that time I ran into one of the girls from the hostel, a beautiful indian girl with an english accent, basically my Kryptonite.  She convinced me to stay and hang out with her, which of course I acquiesced to.  I kicked it with her and her friends at the club for the rest of the night and then went home.[gallery orderby="title"]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[La Boca]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/01/20/la-boca/"/>
    <updated>2010-01-20T09:25:57-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2010/01/20/la-boca</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The day after La Bomba I did a walking tour of La Boca with the love of my life Heidy.  It's a really cool area despite existing solely for the purpose of entertaining tourists.  There's about 4 blocks of La Boca which are safe for tourists, and the rest, "the real Boca" is very dangerous.  The touristy area of La Boca is extremely colorful and all the houses are painted multiple colors because when they were painted about a hundred years ago, the poor would steal paint at night from the port ships and just grab any color and put it on their house and then come back the next night and grab a different color and slowly paint their house in this manner.  La Boca is also famous for being the birthplace of the Tango.  The best part of the Tango is that it seems like a really romantic dance and what not.  The type of thing you learn to do with the love of you life, in my case Heidy, but in reality Heidy informed us that this dance was the dance the sailors did with the hookers.  La Boca was a port, and sailors would come ashore, and of course what do sailors want when they get to port?  So this dance evolved as the dance they did before the other stuff went down.  This may be the funniest thing I've learned in BA so far.</p>

<p>Best part of the day:  There are tango dancers, male and female who approach people of the opposite sex and ask you if you want a picture with them, and they give you a coat and what not so you look like a dancer.  Of course this costs money and I didn't want to pay someone just to take a picture with me.  But this gorgeous girl approaches me and is like do you want to take a picture with me and i'm like no, lo siento, gracias.  And she just goes "why not"? And I just froze, and couldn't come up with a good reason that wouldn't sound like I was cheap or offensive so I just go, OK.  And she smiles, we take some pictures, and I was 20 pesos poorer.  However, the pictures were fun, so all in all I was happy.[gallery orderby="title"]</p>

<p>[gallery orderby="title"]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
