<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Malaysia | Half Black Half Amazing]]></title>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/categories/malaysia/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-10T16:34:03-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Blake Johnson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Travel]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-31T12:17:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/12/31/the-year-in-travel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I figured that coming to the end of the year and about the 3/4 mark of the trip it'd be worth doing a synopsis of everything that's happened so far.  At this point I've been on the road for a little more than four and a half months, having left NYC August 13th.</p>

<p>I've been to 33 "places", (meaning spots I've spent at least one night in) and 12 countries.  I think Brazil is the place I spent the most time at around 1 month and will add another 2 weeks in February.</p>

<p>Excluding the countries I actually visited, I've met fellow travelers from:</p>

<p>Sweeden
Denmark
Holland
England
Australia
Ireland
France
Spain
Bolivia
Scotland
Germany
Italy
Croatia
South Africa
Russia
Austria
Israel
Mexico
Bulgaria</p>

<p>Definitely the most common countries are Aussies by far, then English, Israel, then oddly Sweeden.</p>

<p>Next year I'll be in Argentina (Mendoza, Bariloche &amp; El Calafate (Patagonia)), back to NYC for one week at the end of January.  Then two weeks in Northern Brazil and Salvador, then making my way down to Rio for carnival, then to Peru for two weeks (Lima and Cusco for Machu Pichu) then finally home to NYC with a possible stop in SF for skiing and/or Austin Texas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regrets]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/27/regrets/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-27T01:30:14-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/27/regrets</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Ever since I went to Mexico when I was a Junior in High School and was too much of a p*ssy to try and kiss this girl who I had a crush on and who I later learned had a crush on me I decided I’d live with no regrets.  I’ve never wanted to regret either doing something, or being too scared to not do it (more the latter as it’s hard to control what you WILL regret doing).  However, the biggest regret I’ve had in a while has been missing my plane in KL.  It cost me about 400 USD because apparently the ticket I had was a promotional no refund whatsoever ticket.  I spoke to the supervisor of all of Malaysia airlines and he was still unwilling to budge whatsoever.  They couldn’t put me on standby because all their planes were overbooked.  I understood his position given that it was entirely my fault for missing my plane, not his.  I lost a night in Shanghai and 400 USD as a result of my stupidity.  For most of my life, my dad and I have argued over being late/early to things, me insisting that we were wasting time by showing up early.  I’ve taken probably 50 or so flights in my life, and have never missed one, except for one post green key one but that was unavoidable as I knew if I drank until 6AM it was highly likely I’d miss my flight and accepted that when I had my first beer.  Other than that though I roll into the airport at the last possible minute and always have gotten on my flight with no problems.  This is the first and last flight I will miss as I am conceding to my father that even a 49/50 hit rate makes the one I missed a higher cost than all the potential hours I’d lose by getting to the airport early for the rest of my life.  Losing out on a night in Shanghai and 400 USD was crushing, and I’d easily give up an extra hour for every flight I’d saved on the past 49 to have made my plane that morning.  That said, if it costs me 400 USD and one day to learn that lesson at 26, maybe it was well worth it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur]]></title>
    <link href="http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/27/kuala-lumpur/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-27T00:28:38-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blake41.github.com/halfblackhalfamazing/blog/2009/10/27/kuala-lumpur</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I left early in the morning from Vientiane in order to catch my flight to Kuala Lumpur.  I emailed my old friend from Dartmouth/Novack Café to let him know I was headed to Singapore and to make dinner plans for that evening.  However, I found out the Kuala Lumpur is in Malaysia and not Singapore!  Who knew.  It’s weird that I thought that, because I had looked at the map when I was coming East from India through KL and saw that Singapore was on the bottom of Malaysia, and knew I was in Malaysia when I stopped over in KL on the way to Hong Kong, but somehow I got the idea that it was in both Singapore and Malaysia?  Anyways dear reader, I can assure you that Singapore is a different country than Malaysia.<br/>
Other than that, I have very little to say.  I went to see this giant cave with a big gold statue out front that is used as a temple but it was pretty underwhelming.  On the whole KL was pretty boring.  The highlight of my time there was missing my flight and spending a whole day in the airport.  I met a Chinese girl who was on her way back from Australia and who lived in Beijing.  We ended up kicking it for like 6 hours and made plans to meet up when I got to Beijing.</p>

<p>[gallery]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
